# **DAVID DANIEL FUENTEZ HERNANDEZ**

### **COMPUTER ENGINEER**







Siguatepeque, Comayagua Honduras

#### ABOUT ME

Versatile and able to multi-task. Experience in the planning and development of POA plans through the coordination and participation of the entire team.

Ability to perform with ease in the administrative tasks of the company, both individually and as part of a team.

## EDUCATION

## Universidad Tecnológica de Honduras 5th year Computer Science Engineering, 2024

- Promedio académico 81%
  - · Approximate graduation date: first week of June 2024.

#### COURSES

#### **NDG Linux Essentials**

Cisco Networking Academy, 2023

#### **NDG Linux Unhatched**

Cisco Networking Academy, 2023

## 5G, AI, Cloud Computing and HMS technologies

Huawei, Seeds for The Future, 2022

## Master en JavaScript: Aprender JS, jQuery, Angular, NodeJS

Udemy, Víctor Robles, Junio 2023

#### Typescript: The Complete developer's Guide

Udemy, Stephen Grider, Junio 2023

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## Mobile and Web application development.

DaHu Company Services, Siguatepeque

- 2022 to date.
- Environments in Flutter, Net Maui, LAMP, HTML, CSS JavaScript, Java, C#.

#### Teacher/Tutor

Blessing to the Nations, Siguatepeque.

• 2020 - 2023.

#### **Accounting Assistant**

Blessing to the Nations, Siguatepeque.

• 2022 - 2024.

# **Customer Service Agent**

Startek, Amazon Inc, San Pedro Sula

• 2019

# • SKILLS

- Dart
- C#
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- Python
- Excel
- Firebase
- MySQL
- Oracle Database
- NextJs
- Microsoft Word

## • LANGUAGES

## **English Language**

- Intermediate Oral Level.
- Intermediate Written Level.

# **Spanish Language**

Native